Guide to the University Center Activities and Events, 1999-2012
Duke University. University Archives
University Center Activities and Events, 1999-2012
Duke University. University Archives
Duke University. Office of Student Affairs. University Center Activities and Events.
0.5 linear feet Extent: 500 Items
University Center Activities and Events (UCAE) strives to offer the Duke community and external customers help with event planning and campus programming needs. Collection includes publications, programs, and media. The collection ranges in date from 1999-2012.
UA.09.12.0001
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Patrons must sign the Acknowledgement of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights form before using this collection.
Also, all or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. Consequently, there may be a 24-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The University Center Activities and Events were received by the University Archives as a transfer in 2012.
Detailed Description of Collection
- Container List, 1999-2012, (1 box)
  This material was created by the Leadership Development and Social Action Team within University Center Activities and Events.
  - Publications, 1999-2012 (Box 1)
  - Leadership Events, 2004-2008 (Box 1)
  - Programs, 1999-2012 (Box 1)
  - Student-Led Programs, 2006-2010 (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Student Leadership Conference Slides, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Student Leadership Conference Photos, 2008 (Box 1)
  - Campus Events Slides, undated (Box 1)
  - Beaufort Leadership Retreat, 2002 (VHS Master) (c.1, c.2) *User copy must be made for use. (Box 1)
  - Beaufort Leadership Presentation, 2002 (Mini-DV Master) *User copy must be made for use. (Box 1)
  - Electronic media: one CD w/ Student Affairs Leadership and Service Program, 2006, one CD with Awards ceremony, 2006 April 24 (all images), one CD with Office of Student Activities and Facilities images from student events 2007[?], one CD with Office of Student Activities and Facilities images from on-campus events such as Mo Rocca, Take Back the Night, 2005-2007[?], two 3.5" diskettes, undated regarding Griffith Award Info, GA Breakfast (Box 1)